[Music]
Woke up feeling like I'm 90 years old.
My back's on fire. My story's been told.
Used to bounce back like a rubber band.
Now it's too full. Days of this recovery
trap. Today hangover used to be one. The
party still fun, but the damage is done.
I double the price from a good time run.
Today hangover orange used to be one
last that tequila felt like a great
plan. This morning I'm dying. Can't even
stand. Hair of the dog but the dog bit
back. Now I'm trapped in the cycle of
panic attack. Today hangover it used to
be one. The shots are so smooth. Now I'm
under the gun. I'm running like a fool
but the morning's no fun.
Yeah. Today hangover it used to be one
[Music]
used to dance still don't know can my
head I'm googling ready from the comfort
of beds and Gatorade can't make this
right
guess I'll feel normal by Tuesday night.
[Music]
[Applause]
The clock's my enemy. Time's not my
friend. Can't stop the party, but I
can't pretend. Truth was a blessing I
never did see. Now it's two day pay back
for every spree.
[Music]